- 有个坏消息   - 什么
- Hey, guys. I got some bad news.     - What?
那不是卖报纸的好方法 试试"快报 快来买喔"
That's no way to sell newspapers. Try, "Extra! Extra! Read all about it!"
不 摩妮卡的餐厅在纽约邮报上的评价很差
No. Monica's restaurant got a horrible review in the Post.
我不希望她看到它 所以跑遍附近报摊买下所有报纸
I didn't want her to see it, so I ran around and bought all the copies I could find.
这真的很糟糕 我一直都被批评的很凶
Man, this is bad. And I've had my share of bad reviews.
我还记得我第一次被赞美
I still remember my first good one:
"在"我们的小镇"里 其他的事都很糟糕
"Everything else in this production of Our Town was simply terrible.
乔伊·崔比亚尼是个无底洞"
Joey Tribbiani was abysmal."
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我的天啊 看看这些报纸
Oh, my God! Look at all the newspapers.
评价一定很不错 对吧
It must be a good review. Is it great?
我的天啊
Oh, dear God.
但好消息是两条街里没有人会知道
But the good news is, no one in a two-block radius will ever know.
- 曼哈顿其他的人呢    - 他们都会知道
- What about the rest of Manhattan?     - Yeah, they all know.
- 天啊 这太可怕了   - 很遗憾
- Oh, my God, this is horrible.     - I'm sorry.
我觉得好丢脸
I'm so humiliated.
人家不是说没有所谓的负面报导
But you know what they say, there is no such thing as bad press.
你不觉得"鬼头刀难吃极了"是负面报导吗
You don't think that, um, "the chef's mahi-mahi was awful-awful" is bad press?
那又不是我写的
I didn't write it.
- 天啊 他说的对吗 我很逊吗    - 不
- God, is he right? Am I awful?     - Oh, no!
摩妮卡 听我说
Hey, Monica, listen to me, okay?
我这么做不只因为我是你的朋友
I'm not saying this because I'm your friend, I say it because it's true.
你的食物是个无底洞
Your food is abysmal!
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
- 罗斯   - 什么
- Ross?     - What? What?
- 我快吓死了   - 是吗
- I am freaking out!     - Are you?
我的预产期是一星期后
My due date is in one week!
- 你为什么不睡觉    - 只剩七天
- What are you doing up?     - That is seven days.
我睡前喝了太多水 我们可不可以晚一点再…
Look, I had a lot of water. Can we do this after...?
不 罗斯
No, no, no, no, Ross!
我们没有准备任何东西
Please, come on. We do not have any big stuff we need.
我们没买尿布台或摇篮
We don't have a changing table. We do not have a crib.
- 我们甚至没买尿布   - 你现在提起尿布太有趣了
- We do not have a diaper service.     - Funny you should mention diapers.
- 我是认真的   - 没什么好担心的
- I'm serious.     - Look. There's nothing to worry about.
西10街有家婴儿用品专卖店
We have plenty of time. There's a baby furniture store on West 10th.
我们到那里去…
Tomorrow, we'll go there...
- 买我们需要的东西 好吗   - 好吧 谢谢你 太棒了
- ...and we'll get everything we need. Okay?     - Okay. Thank you. That's great.
西10街在哪里 那里有家鞋店…
Wait, where on West 10th? There's a really cute shoe store...
好吧 如果你要这么做
Okay. If, uh... If you're gonna do this...
我要那么做 所以…
...then I'm gonna go do that, so...
- 等一下 罗斯 抱歉 还有一件事   - 对
- Wait, Ross! I'm sorry, one more thing.     - Yeah.
我们的情况 我们对彼此的意义…
Um, our situation, you know, um, what we mean to each other...
我是说我们要一起抚养孩子 我们要住在一起…
...and, I mean, we're having this baby together and we live together...
那…那不是很奇怪吗
Isn't that...? Isn't that weird?
喔…
Well, uh...
我只是在开玩笑 你可以去上厕所了
I'm just kidding. You can go pee. Ha, ha.
我们约好在这里
Hey, I can't remember. Did we say we were gonna meet here...
- 或是在电影院里碰面 - 我们约好在电影院里碰面 但…
-...or at the movie?     - At the movies...
- 我们到电影院见   - 既然你来了…
- I'll see you there.     - Joey. Now that you're here...?
跟你们碰面之前先和你们混
Sure, I can hang out till I have to meet you.
- 你为什么不去    - 我要去面试一个新工作
- How come you're not going?     - I've got a job interview to get ready for.
- 我以为你已经有工作了   - 大家还说你不太关心别人
- I thought you already have a job.     - And people say you don't pay attention.
这份工作比较好 它是一家公司的副总栽…
This is a much better job. It's vice president of the company...
这家公司为其他公司
...that does data reconfiguration...
做资料重构
...and statistical factoring and for other companies.
- 你怎么知道该怎么做    - 那就是我现在的工作
- Wow. How do you know how to do that?     - That's what I do now.
- 乔伊 来试吃一下   - 什么
- Joey? Come taste this.     - What is it?
还记得给我烂评价的那个人吗  喔…
Remember the guy that gave me a bad review? Well...
我要跟他报复
...I'm getting my revenge.
你把他煮了
You cooked him?
不 他在新校开了一堂课…
No. He teaches a course on food criticism at The New School.
我要他再试试我的马赛鱼汤
Before we go to the movies, I want to make him try my bouillabaisse again.
我等不及要看明天的报纸头条
Ugh, I can't wait to read the front page tomorrow:
"餐厅评监家承认 我错怪了摩妮卡"
"Restaurant reviewer admits: 'I was wrong about Monica."'
头版
The front page?
你真的活在你的小世界里 对吧
You really do live in your own little world, don't you?
（小星星）
需要我们做外送服务吗  盖勒先生跟盖勒太太
Do you want these delivered, Mr. and Mrs. Geller?
- 不   - 不
- Oh, no, no, no. No, no.     - Heh. No, no.
- 我们没有结婚   - 我们的孩子快出世了…
- We're not married.     - We are having a baby together...
但我们没有结婚
...but we're not involved.
我是说 我们曾经交往过…
I mean, uh, we... We were seeing each other a while ago...
之后我们变成了朋友 有天晚上我们喝醉了…
...but then we were just friends, and then there was one drunken night...
对 陌生人 我们需要外送服务
Or, yes, stranger, we'd like this delivered, please.
- 麻烦你填一下住址   - 好的
- Why don't you fill out this address card?     - Oh, okay.
- 你挑了很多恐龙   - 对
- I noticed you picked out a lot of dinosaurs.     - Oh, yeah.
所以那也就是为什么我们没有结婚
That's one of the reasons why we are not a couple.
我选了那些 我是古生物学家
I chose those. I'm a paleontologist.
真的吗 那太酷了
Really? That is so cool.
别太夸他 你可能以为他是博士 但事实上不然
Oh, don't get too worked up over it. It sounds like he's a doctor, but he's not.
不 我喜欢古生物学
Oh, no. I'm fascinated by paleontology.
- 你看过华特·艾瓦瑞兹的书吗    - 它是我的教科书
- Have you read the Walter Alvarez book?     - Yeah, heh, I teach it in class.
我站在收银台 手里拿着信用卡 却觉得很无聊
Oh, my God. Standing at a cash register, I'm holding a credit card, and I'm bored.
我喜欢你住的社区 街角有家很棒的健身房
I love your neighborhood. There's a great gym around the corner from your building.
- 那是我的健身房   - 我看得出来你有健身
- That's my gym.     - I could tell you work out.
一位会健身的古生物学家 你跟印第安纳·琼斯一样
A paleontologist who works out. You're like Indiana Jones.
我是跟印第安纳·琼斯一样
I am like Indiana Jones.
（中央咖啡厅）
嗨 菲比
Hi, Pheebs.
宝宝的东西买得怎么样了
Hey! Oh, how did baby shopping go?
太棒了 我们需要的东西都买到了
It was great! We got everything we needed.
罗斯差点拿到清单上没有的东西
Oh, and Ross almost got something that wasn't on the list.
一个妓女
Ahem, a whore.
- 什么   - 我们正在付帐
- What?     - We were paying for our stuff...
这个女销售员开始泡他
...and this sales woman just started flirting with him.
你能相信吗
Can you believe that?
- 她知道你们没有结婚吗    - 知道
- Did she know you two weren't married?     - Yeah.
天啊 那… 一个女人在泡一个单身男人
Oh, my God. Well, the idea... A woman flirting with a single man?
- 我们得通知教会的长老   - 不
- We must alert the church elders.     - No.
你不了解 你没看到她多不要脸
You don't understand. You didn't see how brazen she was.
- 你好像在吃醋   - 我才没有
- Sounds like you're a little jealous.     - No, I'm not.
我只是觉得那是不对的 我是说我就快生了…
I just think it's wrong. I mean, here I am, about to pop...
他在荡妇专门店泡女人
...and he's out picking up some shopgirl at Sluts-R-Us?
真的有那种地方吗
Is that a real place?
他们有缺人吗
Are they hiring?
嘿 菲比 肥婆
Hey, Phoebe. Fatty.
你为什么那么高兴
Hey, Chandler, why so fancy?
我得到一个面试机会
Well, I got a job interview. Big deal, too.
薪水比较高 我要做资料重构的工作
It's more money. I'd be doing data reconfiguration and statistical factoring.
- 我知道有个人就做那一行   - 那就是我
- I think I know someone who does that.     - Me. I do that.
我看起来还好吧 我好紧张
So seriously, do I look okay? I'm nervous.
对 你看起来很棒
Oh, yeah. You... Really, you look great.
别抱太高的希望
You know, just don't get your hopes up.
- 为什么    - 你要去面试
- Why not?     - Well, the interview.
- 所以呢    - 你知道的
- What about it?     - You know.
你无法给人留下良好的第一印象
You don't make a very good first impression.
- 什么    - 喔 你不知道啊
- What?     - Oh, you don't know.
- 你是说真的吗    - 我第一次见到你 你是这样的
- Are you serious?     - Yes. When I first met you, you were like:
我就觉得…
I was like:
我怎么了
What is it that I do?
你太努力 想要说笑话…
It's just, like, you're trying too hard, always making jokes.
你太急了
You just... You come off a little needy.
我们第一次见面时 你喜欢我吗
Did you like me when we first met?
钱德 我不想骗你
Chandler, I'm not gonna lie to you.
但我要离开了
But I am gonna run away from you.
嗨 我是摩妮卡·盖勒 亚利山多洛斯的主厨
Hi. I'm Monica Geller, chef at Allessandro's.
现在还是
Still?
你说的评论有点不公平…
I think the things you said were unfair...
我要你再试试我的马赛鱼汤
...and I would like you to give my bouillabaisse another chance.
我看不出来 我有什么原因再试一次
I don't see any reason why I'd do that to myself again.
你不吃就倒霉
Either eat it or be in it.
汤匙
Spoon?
- 你觉得呢    - 我很为难…
- So, what do you think?     - I'm torn...
不知道要老实说还是避免自己被打一顿
...between my integrity and my desire to avoid a beating.
但我得老实说 你的汤是个无底洞
But I must be honest. Your soup is abysmal.
做的好 我们应该离开这里 新的一班要上课了
Thattagirll Eh? We should get out of here, there's a new class coming in.
欢迎大家来上烹调入门
Welcome to Introduction to Cooking. Before we start...
谁能告诉我荷兰酸味蘸酱 贝纳斯酱的差别
...can anyone tell me the difference between hollandaise and bearnaise sauce?
- 我知道   - 请说
- I can.     - Okay, go ahead.
它们都放了蛋黄跟奶油
Well, um, they both have a egg yolk and butter base.
但贝纳斯酱有放葱 雪维菜 跟最重要的小龙艾
But a bearnaise, um, has shallots, chervil, and most importantly, tarragon.
- 非常好 你叫什么名字   - 摩妮卡
- Ha, ha, very good. What's your name?     - Monica.
- 你来当班长   - 好吧
- Monica, you go to the head of the class!     - Okay!
这些玩意占好多空间喔
All this stuff takes up a lot of room.
你说你要留班一辈子 你有多认真
Hey, how, uh, serious are you about keeping Ben in your life?
我的儿子吗 我非常认真
My son? Pretty serious.
嗨 凯蒂 你来这里做什么
Oh, hey, Katie. What are you doing here?
外送部忘了这个
The delivery went out and I realized they forgot this.
这一定很明显 因为它是你店里唯一剩下的东西
Ah, it must have been obvious, since it was the only thing left in your store.
听着 老实说 我的工作不包括送货到家服务
Listen, to be honest, home deliveries aren't really part of my job description.
我是来这里约你的
Oh, um, I actually came here to ask you out.
哇 那听起来很棒
Oh. Wow. Uh, yeah, that sounds great.
我要把这个放回我的口袋 假装那件事没有发生过
I'm just gonna put this back in my pocket and pretend that didn't happen.
现在我有空 你要去喝咖啡吗…
Uh, I'm free now. You want to grab some coffee...?
- 当然好   - 荡妇
- Sure.     - Horny bitch.
你是荡妇 你是荡妇 不不
No, you're a horny bitch! No, you're a horny bitch!
不 你是荡妇
No, you're a horny bitch!
祝你们玩得愉快
So you guys go, have a really good time.
我去拿我的外套跟鞭子
I'm just gonna grab my coat. And, uh, my whip.
因为我像印第安纳·琼斯
You know, because of Indiana Jones.
不是因为我喜欢性虐待
Not because I'm into S&M.
我没有怪癖 你知道吗
I'm not into anything weird, you know? Heh.
我只喜欢一般的性爱
Just normal sex.
我去拿外套
So I'm gonna grab my coat.
你今天过得很不错嘛 泡老爸 赚大佣金
So you had a good day, huh? Big commission, picked up a daddy.
你没问题吧
Are you okay with this?
当然 拜托 你们好好玩吧
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please. You guys have fun.
- 好吧   - 对
- Okay. Heh.     - Yeah.
很高兴能见到你
It was nice to see you.
我也是 你看起来好极了
Oh, and it was great to see you too. And you look fantastic.
虽然你有颗扣子忘了扣
Although you missed a button.
事实上我…
Oh, actually, I, um...
好吧 我知道你想做什么
Oh, okay, I see what you're doing there.
我不敢相信我的形象有那么糟
I can't even believe this. I really come off that badly?
那没什么 不久后你会静下来…
Ugh, it's okay. You calm down after a while...
大家会了解你有多棒
...and then people can see how sweet and wonderful you are.
好吧 因为我相信这次面试会维持好几个星期
Good. Because I'm sure this interview's gonna last a couple of weeks.
好吧 别惊慌 我会帮你的
All right, don't freak out, okay? I will help you.
- 你什么时候要出发    - 一小时后
- How long before you have to leave?     - An hour.
- 我帮不了你   - 菲比…
- I can't help you.     - Phoebe...
我们得尽力而为 我是面试官 我第一次跟你见面
We'll do our best. I'm the interviewer and I'm meeting you for the first time.
- 好吧   - 请进 我是蕾吉娜·菲兰吉斯
- Okay.     - Hi. Come on in. I'm Regina Phalanges.
- 钱德宾   - 宾
- Chandler Bing.     - Oh, Bing.
- 你的名字很罕见   - 你应该见见我的巴达叔叔
- What an unusual name.     - Well, you should meet my Uncle Bada.
我自己出去
I'll let myself out.
你的意大利宽条面有点干 你有放起司吗
Your alfredo's dry. Did you use your cheese?
你说"放"是指 "把它当作菜前的点心吃掉了"吗
When you say "use," do you mean "eat as a pre-cooking snack"?
- 奶油呢    - 起司让我口渴
- And the cream?     - Cheese makes me thirsty.
- 好吧 我们继续   - 好吧
- Okay. Let's move on.     - All right.
摩妮卡做的菜味道很香
Oh. Something smells good over at Monica's station.
天啊 这真的是太好吃了 你从来没有做过这个
My God! This is absolutely amazing! You've never made this before?
不 我不懂烹饪
Oh, no. I don't know anything about cooking.
我不知道水冒泡后要做什么
I had to ask what it was called when the water makes those bubbles.
向主厨致意
Wow. Hats off to the chef.
你嘴里都是东西 我听不到
I'm sorry, your mouth was full. I didn't hear what you said.
- 跟谁致意    - 主厨
- Hats off to who now?     - The chef!
没错
Heh, that's right!
你会发现我不会事必躬亲
I think you'll find if I work here that I don't micromanage.
我不害怕沟通
I don't shy away from delegating.
那真的很棒 但别谈那些你不会做的事…
Mm-hm. That's good to know. But let's stop focusing on what you don't do...
我们来谈谈你会做的事
...and focus on what you do do.
我会…
What I do do...
支援为我工作的人
is manage to, uh, create an atmosphere of support for the people working with me.
你刚刚回避的很巧妙
I see. Nice sidestep on the "do do" thing.
- 那是我做过最难的事   - 你得出发了
- Hardest thing I've ever done in my life.     - Oh, you gotta go!
- 别担心 你准备好了   - 真的吗
- Okay, don't worry. You're ready.     - Really?
当然 跟着你的直觉走 你会很棒的
Absolutely! Just fight all your natural instincts, and you'll be great.
摩妮卡 我的明星学生
Ah, Monica, my star student.
之前你那么叫我
Heh. You called me that before...
所以我用锡箔纸做了一颗星星
...so I took the liberty of fashioning a star out of foil.
别觉得压力太大 如果你喜欢我的饼干 给我一颗星星
Now, no pressure. If you like my cookies, you give me the star.
一颗星星
Wow, a star!
我知道你们都恨我 对不起 但我不在乎
I know you all hate me, and I'm sorry, but I don't care.
- 好吧 乔伊 下一个是你   - 是的
- Okay, Joey, you're up next.     - Yeah.
天啊 这真的是太棒了
Oh, my God! This is amazing!
你得到优等
You get an A.
我在学校里得到优等 我是个书呆子了
I got an A? In school? Hey, I'm a dork!
乔伊 我非常以你为荣
Joey, I'm so proud of you.
- 我想你该把你的星星给他   - 你说什么
- I think you should give him your star.     - Excuse me?
- 他不知道自己在做什么   - 我们是初学者
- He doesn't even know what he's doing.     - We're all beginners.
- 没有人知道自己在做什么   - 我知道 我是职业主厨
- Nobody knows what they're doing.     - I do. I'm a professional chef!
少来了 这又不是法律影集
Oh, relax. It's not a courtroom drama.
如果你是专业主厨 为什么要上初级烹调课
What are you doing taking Introduction to Cooking?
就是嘛
Yeah!
抱歉 我是亚利山多洛斯餐厅的主厨…
I'm sorry. It's just that, um, I cook at this restaurant, Allessandrds...
我得到了很差的评论
...and, um, I just got a really bad review.
- 亚利山多洛斯 我喜欢那个地方   - 是吗
- Oh, Allessandro's? I love that place!     - You do?
你是个很棒的主厨 但你的个性有点…
Yes, you're an excellent chef. As a person you're a little...
- 我是很疯狂"但你喜欢那里的食物    - 非常喜欢
- Oh, totally crazy, but you liked the food?     - Ha, ha. Very much.
好吧 那么我不赖 我是个好主厨 好吧
Okay, then. I don't stink. I'm a good chef! Okay.
我不想离开 我玩得很开心
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I don't want to go. I'm having fun.
你们有付学费吗
Actually, did either of you pay for this class?
如果我的朋友说 我们该走了 我们就该离开
Hey, if my friend says it's time to go, it's time to go!
我在我的公司负责KLS系统
Also, I was the point person on my company's transition...
转换到GR6系统的工作
...from the KL5 to GR6 systems.
- 你一定忙得不可开交   - 没错 没错
- You must have had your hands full.     - That I did. That I did.
我们来谈谈你的责任吧
So let's talk a little bit about your duties.
我的责任
My duties?
好吧
All right.
你将负责一整个部门 所以你得负起很多责任
You'll be heading a whole division, so you'll have a lot of duties.
- 我了解   - 你手下会有30个人…
- I see.     - But there'll be 30 people under you...
你可以把很多工作分给他们
...so you can dump a certain amount on them.
- 那太好了   - 我们可以仔细地…
- Good to know.     - We could go into detail...
不 我求你
No, don't, I beg of you.
好吧 我们会在星期一回复你
All right, then. We'll have a definite answer for you on Monday.
但我相信 你在这里会适应的很好
But I can say with some confidence, you'll fit in well here.
- 真的吗    - 当然
- Really?     - Absolutely.
- 你可以放轻松 你表现的很好   - 谢谢
- You can relax. You did great.     - I gotta say, thank you.
我真的很紧张 大家都说我太喜欢讲笑话 缓和气氛
I was really nervous. I'm told I come on too strongly, too many jokes.
要避开"责任"的问题真的很难
And then it was really hard to side step that "duty" thing.
责任
Duties?
笨蛋
Doodies?
傻瓜
Poo?
天啊 这不算好吗 面试已经结束
Oh, my God. This doesn't count. Okay? The interview was over.
那才是真正的钱德宾 这只是个疯子
That was the real Chandler Bing. This is some crazy guy in the hall.
叫警卫来 走廊上有个疯子
Call security! There's a crazy guy out in the hall!
傻瓜
Poo?
我期待你的来电
I'll look forward to your call.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 你约会回来了    - 你还好吗
- You're back from your date.     - How are you?
我很好 但那不重要 重要的是她还好吗
I'm fine. But that's not important. What's important is how was she?
我们玩得很高兴 我们一起去喝咖啡
Uh, it was fun. We just had coffee.
喝咖啡 在桌下调情
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh, coffee, a little rub-rub-rub under the table?
怎么了 你不喜欢凯蒂
Heh, what's going on? Do you not like Katie?
不 她很好
No. No, she was nice.
她有点淫荡 但谁不是呢
I mean, she was a little slutty, but who isn't?
我喜欢她
Well, I liked her.
你当然喜欢她 只要猩猩叫你印第安纳你也会跟他约会
Of course you did. You'd date a gorilla if it called you Indiana Jones.
你拿到今天的怀孕荷尔蒙报告吗
Did you get a fresh batch of pregnancy hormones today?
不 那只是… 凯蒂让我觉得困扰
No. It's just that... Katie bothered me.
为什么 她有哪里不好
Why? What was wrong with her?
她没有哪里不好 她非常可爱
Ugh, there was nothing wrong with her. All right? She was perfectly lovely.
- 好吧 怎么了    - 我不希望你跟她约会
- Okay. So, what's the matter?     - I don't want you to date her.
为什么 你在吃醋吗
Heh, what? Why? What, are you jealous?
对 但不是因为我要你跟我交往
Yes. And not because I want you to go out with me.
因为我不希望你跟任何人交往
Because I don't want you to go out with anybody.
光想到这一点我就不舒服 那是不对的…
I know it's a terrible thing to even think this and it's inappropriate...
但我希望你每天24小时都能陪在我身边
...but I want you to be at my constant beck and call, 24 hours a day.
我非常抱歉 但那就是我的感觉
I'm very sorry, but that is just the way that I feel.
- 好吧   - 什么
- Okay.     - What?
我不约会 我会…
I won't date. I'll, uh...
我会一直陪着你
I'll be here with you all the time.
真的吗
Really?
但我的要求很无理
But I'm being so unreasonable.
没错 但你可以无理取闹 你怀了我们的宝宝
True, but you're allowed to be unreasonable. You're having our baby.
罗斯 谢谢你
Oh, Ross, thank you. Thank you.
你觉得好多了吗
You feel better?
真的没有 你把宝宝压在我的膀胱上…
No, not really. You're pressing the baby into my bladder...
现在我得去尿尿
...and now I have to pee. Sorry.
- 好吧   - 瑞秋
- Okay.     - Rash?
- 什么事    - 只有一件事…
- Yeah?     - Just one thing. Um...
我们住在一起 你怀了我们的孩子 我不跟任何人约会
We live together. You're having our baby. I'm not gonna see anybody else.
你确定你不想更进一步吗
Are you sure you don't want something more?
我不知道 或许吧…
Wow. I don't know, maybe...
瑞秋 我只是在开你玩笑
Oh, Rach, I was just messing around. Heh.
- 就像我要尿尿时你做的一样   - 我就知道
- Like you did when I had to pee?     - Oh! Ha! I knew that.
我就知道 我也是在开你玩笑
I knew that! I was just messing with you too!
好吧 因为你看起来似乎…
Okay. Because for a minute you seemed...
- 不 那是…   - 像是你真的…
- No, no, no, no. No! It's just... Ha! -...like you actually...
那只是因为我很会开玩笑
That's just because I'm such a good messer!
- 瑞秋   - 什么
- Rash?     - Yeah?
- 你要上厕所   - 对
- The bathroom?     - Right.
我非常愉快 我学会了烤东西 吃美食
I had a great time. I learned how to bake, ate great food.
这是我七年级后第一次得到优等 我甚至没跟老师上床
The first A I've gotten since 7th grade and I didn't have to sleep with the teacher.
- 你看"初级戏剧班"   - 对
- Oh, look. Acting for Beginners.     - Yeah.
你想更满意自己吗
Wanna feel good about yourself?
- 管它的   - 好吧
- What the hell!     - Okay.
我们从基础开始吧
All right, let's start with some basics.
谁能告诉我后台跟前台的差别
Can anybody tell me what the difference between upstage and downstage is?
对 这个点子很蠢
Yeah, this was a stupid idea.